(中央咖啡厅)
嘿 我们所有人当中 你们认为下一个结婚的会是谁？
Hey, out of all of us, who do you think will get married next?
大概是摩妮卡和钱德
Probably Monica and Chandler.
能不能给我一包新港淡烟？
Hi, could I have a pack of Newport Lights?
我们没有卖烟 对面的书报摊有卖
Oh, um, uh, we don't sell cigarettes, but they do across the street.
那太好了 谢谢
That'd be great. Thanks.
我的天
Oh, my God.
梅莉莎伍伯 我没有力气应付她
Melissa Worbert. I don't think I have the energy for this.
我的天 瑞瑞葛林？
Oh, my God! Ray-Ray Green?
梅莉莎 嘿
Melissa. Hey.
我们姐妹会期刊 连续7期都说你失踪了
You've been MIA for seven sorority newsletters.
你怎么了？
What's up with you?
我们到那边去再说吧
Why don't I tell you over here?
上次我听说你要结婚了
So last I heard you were gonna get married.
哦
Oh.
可怜的瑞瑞
Poor Ray-Ray.
不 我其实很好
Oh, no, no. It's... It's good. It's all good.
- 我现在替罗夫罗兰工作   - 闭嘴
- I actually work at Ralph Lauren.     - Shut up!
我才不闭嘴 我是 男装运动服饰部门的主管
I will not. Heh, heh. I'm the divisional head of men's sportswear.
不会吧 你跟罗夫是朋友吗？
Oh, shut up more! Are you friends with Ralph?
- 拜托   - 你是吗？
- Oh, please. Ha.     - Are you?
不是
No.
我们一定要一起吃个饭 你明天晚上做什么？
Listen, we have to have dinner. What are you doing tomorrow?
- 明天 我不知道   - 现在你知道了  你要和我吃晚饭
- Oh, tomorrow. I don't know. Um...     - You're having dinner with me.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我要走了 看到你真好
I've gotta go. This has been so great, Ray-Ray.
哦 这儿
Oh, there you are.
打电话给我 这是我的名片
Um, so listen, just call me. Here's my card.
哇 谢谢
Oh, wow, thanks.
- 你在做房地产？ - 不 那是旧名片
- Oh, you're in real estate?     - Oh, no, heh, that's an old card.
我必须辞掉那工作去做些…
Um, I got out of that to do something where I could...
可以帮助别人和改变世界的工作
...help people and make a difference.
现在你做什么？
Wow. What do you do now?
宴会规划
I'm a party planner.
- 明天见   - 好
- I'll see you tomorrow.     - Okay.
看谁回来了 是瑞瑞
Hey guys, look who's back. It's Ray-Ray.
那是我大学的朋友梅莉莎
That was my friend, Melissa, from college.
她好像好好玩
She seems really, really fun!
她真的很甜 我们曾经很亲密
She's actually very sweet, and we used to be very close.
等一下 她不是那个你…？
Wait a minute. She's not the one who you?
你怎样？你怎样？
Who you what? Who you what?
- 是   - 哇
- Yes.     - Wow!
哇什么？你怎样？
Wow... Wow, what? Who you what?
没什么大不了
Oh, it's not a big deal.
她们曾经是情人
They were lovers.
- 什么？ - 什么？
- What?     - What?
不 我们不是情人 那又没什么
No, we weren't. It was nothing.
大四的时候 有一天晚上 我们去参加舞会…
It was one night, senior year, and we went to a party...
喝了很多桑格利亚调酒 你知道 结果…
...had a lot of sangria, and you know, ended up...
我们接吻了
...kissing for a bit.
我有两任老婆是同性恋
So that's two of my wives.
这是乐队的所在 这儿是吧台
Okay, so this is where the band is. And here's the bar.
这些大头针上都有人名 瑞秋 你在这里
And all these pins have people's names on them. Rach, here you are.
哦 喔
Oh, wow!
何不给我一杯曼哈顿…
Why don't we just put me with a Manhattan in my hand...
让我和可爱的酒保聊天
...talking to the cute bartender.
大头针不是用来玩的 是不是？
These pins aren't for playing, are they?
红的是我的客人 蓝色的是你的
Okay, the red ones are my guests, and the blue are yours.
真可怜 我只有10个客人
This is so sad. I only have like 10 pins.
钱德 轻松一点 这又不是比赛
Heh, Chandler, relax. It's not a contest.
不是实力相近的比赛
Certainly not a close one.
- 大家好   - 嘿
- Hello.     - Hey.
嘿 瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
不要再想像了
Stop picturing it!
我想这样可以了 座位表好了 这就是我们的婚礼
Okay, I think that's it. The seating chart is done. This is our wedding.
他们看来好像都很开心 不是吗？
Wow. They all look like they're having fun.
我爸妈坐哪里？
So where are my parents gonna be?
如果这是结婚礼堂…
Well, if this is the wedding hall, then, um...
你父母会在皇后区的家里
...your parents would be over here at home in Queens.
他们没有被邀请？太糟了 他们一定会很伤心
They're not invited? Oh, no, they're gonna be crushed!
他们为什么以为会被邀请呢？
Why would they think they're invited?
你问倒我了 我不…
You got me. I don't...
- 乔伊   - 抱歉 我以为父母都会来
- Joey!     - Look, I thought parents were coming.
你的父母会来 钱德的父母也会来
Your parents are coming. Chandler's parents are coming.
罗斯的父母也会来
Ross' parents are coming.
罗斯的父母就是我的父母
Ross' parents are my parents.
看 父母们都会来
Well, see, parents are coming.
- 我们应该请他们   - 拜托 你只是想要增加蓝色大头针
- We should invite them.     - You just want more blue pins.
这实在太惨了
Well, this is just sad.
好啦 也许我可以把他们排进来 不过要重新安排位置
All right. Maybe I can fit them in if I just do some rearranging.
瑞秋可能真的要坐在吧台
Rachel may have to sit at the bar.
没有问题
That is not a problem.
- 也许你可以叫一杯桑格利亚调酒   - 去你的
- Maybe you'll order a little sangria.     - Oh, get out of here!
这是我们的礼服 如果有你喜欢的 可以便宜些
These are our tuxedos. If you like anything, we can make a deal.
全部都可以 但这三件是摩妮卡先核准的
Anything at all. But these are the three that Monica pre-approved.
谢谢你替我们找到关系 瑞秋
Uh, well, thanks a lot for hooking me up.
我想请你做我的客人 参加我们的婚礼
And I want you to know that I want you to attend our wedding as my guest.
我是摩妮卡的伴娘
I'm Monica's maid of honor.
别想把我变成蓝色大头针
Okay, don't try to blue-pin me.
- 那这些呢？这些看起来不错    - 是不错
- Well, these look nice.     - They are nice.
都是帮名人量身打造的 他们穿过后就送回来这儿
When celebrities are done with them, they send them back.
- 你是指像颁奖典礼之后？ - 有些是
- You mean, like, for award shows?     - Some of them.
这都上过红地毯 被人叫着
They've been down the red carpet with people yelling, uh...
"你是穿谁的？你看来棒极了 "
..."Who are you wearing? You look fabulous!"
容我建议你 多看一点ESPN体育台…
Might I suggest watching a little more ESPN...
少看一点艺人八卦节目
...and a little less E!
谁穿过这些？
Okay. Who wore those?
额…
Uh...
- 这是汤姆布若考穿过的   - 不错嘛
- Well, uh, this one's Tom Brokaw.     - Not bad.
这是保罗欧尼尔穿过的
This one is, uh, Paul O'Neil.
他是谁？
Who's that?
他是《洋基队》的球员 真的 多看ESPN
He plays for the Yankees. Seriously, ESPN.
有的时候 开着当背景也好
Just once in a while. Have it on in the background.
这是皮尔斯布洛斯南穿过的
Ooh, this one was Pierce Brosnan.
- 皮尔斯布洛斯南？ - 额
- Pierce Brosnan?     - Uh-huh.
真的吗？
Are you serious?
007？
007?
詹姆士庞德的燕尾服？我一定要穿詹姆士庞德的燕尾服结婚
This is James Bond's tux? Oh, I have to get married in James Bond's tux.
是很酷的礼服
Ha, ha. It's a pretty cool tux.
不只如此 我会是 英格兰最强大的武器
Ah, it's not just that. I would be England's most powerful weapon.
女王陛下的秘密特务 环游世界的负心人
A jet-setting heartbreaker on Her Majesty's secret service.
有杀人执照 什么都不怕的男人
A man who fears no one, with a license to kill.
摩妮卡会不会让我穿这件？
Would Monica let me wear this?
我们应该学真正的玩法
We should really learn how to play the real way.
我喜欢我们的玩法
I like our way.
- 啊   - 嘿 嘿
- Ah!     - Hey, hey!
将军
Chess!
- 走的好   - 是啊
- Nice move.     - Yeah.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
乔伊 我替罗斯和钱德 找到燕尾服 你需要吗？
I hooked Ross and Chandler up with tuxedos. Do you need one?
不 我要主持婚礼 我不要穿燕尾服
No, I'm not wearing a tux.
- 那你要穿什么？ - 多彩的袍子
- What are you gonna wear?     - Multi-colored robes.
也许戴一顶帽子
Ooh, and maybe a hat.
- 摩妮卡知道吗？ - 不知道
- Huh. Does Monica know about this?     - No.
你告诉她时我可以在场吗？
Can I please be there when you tell her?
瑞秋 晚上要不要去看电影？
Hey, Rach, you want to go to a movie tonight?
没办法 我要和梅莉莎吃饭
Oh, I can't. I'm having dinner with Melissa.
我可以跟你去吗？
Can I come?
我不会说话 你只会听见 我摄影机的声音
I won't talk. You'll just hear my video camera.
- 什么？怎么回事？ - 我可以告诉她吗？
- What? What's going on?     - Can I tell her?
你要听真正发生的事 还是乔伊的淫荡版本？
Do you want what happened, or Joey's lewd version?
- 乔伊的   - 好吧
- Joey's.      - Okay.
喂 少来
Okay, come on.
大学时我有一个朋友…
I had this college friend...
我犯了一个很蠢的错误 告诉乔伊有一次…
...and I made the mistake of telling Joey that one time...
她和我接吻了
...she and I, you know, kissed a little bit.
是噢 我相信你们有
Yeah, I'm sure that happened.
- 真的啊   - 当然
- It did.      - Sure.
那真的发生了
Hey, heh. It happened.
是大四那年 有一次姐妹会 开夏威夷主题派对…
Yeah, it was senior year. It was after the Sigma Chi luau...
我和梅莉莎喝得大醉
...and Melissa and I got very drunk.
结果我们两个接吻了 好几分钟呢
And we ended up kissing. For several minutes.
那表示她喝了几杯 轻轻吻在脸颊上
Which means she had a couple spritzers and a peck on the cheek.
- 你为什么要剥夺我的幻想？ - 额
- Why are you taking this away from me? - Ugh.
为什么这么难让你相信？
Why is it so hard for you to believe?
好吧 我不知道你是同性恋
Okay. I just didn't know that you were a lesbian.
我不是说我是同性恋 我只是说那件事发生了
I'm not saying that I'm a lesbian. I'm just saying that this happened.
我只是那觉得很狂野 而你是这么地…
It just seems pretty wild. And you're... You know, so...
乖宝宝
...vanilla.
乖宝宝？我不是乖宝宝 我会做很多疯狂的事
Vanilla? I'm not vanilla. I do lots of crazy things.
我还喝醉了 在拉斯维加斯结婚
I mean, I got drunk and married in Vegas.
和罗斯
To Ross.
这样吧 如果你不相信我…
If you don't believe me...
今晚和我一起去吃饭 她会告诉你
...just come with me to dinner tonight and she'll tell you.
好吧 因为我想像不出来
Okay. Because I can't picture it.
你该看看我脑袋里的画面
You should get inside my head.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
猜我为你的婚礼弄到什么？
Guess what I got for your wedding?
瘦巴巴的女伴？
A freakishly thin date with a hanger for a head?
瑞秋替我弄到一件燕尾服 但不是随便一件
Rachel hooked me up with a tux. But not just any tux.
是蝙蝠侠的
Batman's tux!
- 什么？ - 没错
- What?     - That's right.
特快速做给方基墨 让他穿在票房冠军电影…
Made expressly for Val Kilmer, and worn by him in the hit film...
他演的那部蝙蝠侠电影里
...that Batman film he was in.
你不能穿那件 我要穿名人的燕尾服
You can't wear that. I'm wearing the famous tux.
- 詹姆士庞德的燕尾服      - 那又怎样？
- James Bond's tux.   - So?
那又怎样？如果你穿那件 会让我的不那么特别
If you wear that, it'll make mine less special.
你需要什么东西来让那天特别吗？
You need something to to make it special?
喂 你有了最特别的一样
Hello! You have the most special thing of all.
你娶了你爱的女人
You are marrying the woman you love.
拜托不要抢走我的锋头 拜托拜托？
Don't take away my cool thing. Pretty please?
"拜托拜托？"不怎么007
"Pretty please?" Not very, uh, 007.
如果你要结婚 我不会做任何让你生气的事
If you were getting married, I'd never do anything to upset you.
- 我结婚的时候 你和我妹妹上床   - 那就很007
- You slept with my sister.     - That was pretty 007.
- 嘿   - 嘿 好 你来了
- Hey.     - Hey. Okay, good. You're here.
好 我想出办法来了
All right, I figured it out.
我把这两桌的8个人 加上你父母…
I'm gonna take 2 tables of 8, add your parents...
变成3桌6个人
...and make them into 3 tables of 6.
我已经通知了办酒席的人 要多做两份 都弄好了
And I called the caterer. We are good to go!
他们不来了
Yeah. They're not coming.
什么？
What?
他们觉得 你是因为我才邀请他们的
They think that you only invited them because of me.
他们觉得不被欢迎
They feel unwanted.
真糟糕 那是真的 不过还是很糟糕
That's too bad. It's true. But too bad.
- 摩妮卡 你可以打电话给我妈   - 乔伊
- If you could just call my mom.     - Oh, Joey.
拜托 让她知道你希望他们去
Come on. Just let her know you want them there.
不要忘记 多年来 她送过你很多很多千层面
Let's not forget this is a woman who has sent you many lasagnas.
她哪有
No, she hasn't.
有些没送到你手里不是她的错
Is it her fault if some didn't make it to you?
我要说什么？
What am I gonna say?
告诉她请帖搞乱了 不 怪邮局好了
Just tell them you mixed up invitations. No, no, no, blame it on the post office.
他们最恨邮局 还有爱尔兰人
They hate the post office. And the Irish.
不过我想你不能怪到他们头上
But I don't think you could blame it on them.
喂？你好 崔比亚尼太太吗？ 我是摩妮卡盖勒
Hello? Yeah, hi. Uh, Mrs. Tribbiani? Hi, this is Monica Geller.
我想告诉你 钱德跟我很希望 你们能来参加婚礼
I'm just calling to say that I really hope you can make the wedding.
我们很多请帖都没寄到
Apparently some of our invitations weren't delivered.
我猜又是可恶的邮局搞砸的
Um, I guess there was some screw-up at the damn post office.
就是嘛
Tell me about it.
什么美国邮局嘛？ 更像是美国遗失局
Yeah, the U.S. Post Office? No. More like U.S. Lost Office.
搞什么嘛  都是爱尔兰人吗？
What are they, Irish?
他叫艾伦  我们在一起三年了
Anyway, his name's Allen. And we've been going out for three years.
他是我做宴会规划的第一位客户
He was my first client when I became a party planner.
那时他正要为当时的女朋友 规划一场宴会
He was actually planning a party for his girlfriend at the time.
- 结果就是这样罗  - 不
- Oh, well.     - No.
- 他是雪城大学兄弟会的    - 真好
- Ah. He was Theta Beta Pi at Syracuse.     - Oh! Oh, that's great.
嗯
Mm-hm.
- 菲比 你参加过姐妹会吗？ - 当然
- Phoebe, were you ever in a sorority?     - Of course.
我是大卫生棉条的成员
Yes. I was a, um, Thigh Mega Tampon.
哪一个？
What one?
我们也很庞大 但后来被关掉了…
Yeah, we were huge too. But they had to shut us down...
因为瑞吉娜佛兰姬基死于酒精中毒
...when Regina Phalangie died of alcohol poisoning.
额
Ugh.
真是糟糕 一颗老鼠屎就毁了一锅粥
Isn't it a shame when one girl ruins it for the whole bunch?
嗯
Hmm. Mm-hm. Ugh.
不管了…
Anyway...
讲到喝太多 我告诉菲比…
Speaking of drinking too much, I was, uh, telling Phoebe...
姐妹会开夏威夷派对 很疯的那晚 我们亲吻的事
...about that crazy night after the Sigma Chi luau where we made out.
什么？
What?
记得我们…我们穿着沙龙 还有椰子壳比基尼上衣
Remember we... Come on, we had sarongs on and the coconut bikini tops.
之后我们回到家 在那儿疯癫…
We went back to the house and got really silly...
然后我们接吻了
...and we made out.
瑞瑞 我不知道你在说什么
Wow, Ray-Ray, I have no idea what you're talking about.
真的吗？
Really?
罗斯是蝙蝠侠
Ross is Batman.
他还真会掩护秘密身份 瞒了这么久
Well, he did manage to keep his identity secret for a long time.
瑞秋替罗斯弄到 方基墨在《蝙蝠侠》里穿的燕尾服
Rachel got Ross the tuxedo that Val Kilmer wore in Batman.
蝙蝠侠比詹姆士庞德酷多了
Batman is so much cooler than James Bond.
- 什么啊？007有很多工具   - 蝙蝠侠有工具腰带
- What? 007 has all those gadgets.     - Batman has a utility belt.
- 007有很炫的车   - 蝙蝠侠有蝙蝠车
- 007 has a fancy car.     - Batman has the Batmobile.
- 007有很多女人   - 蝙蝠侠有罗宾
- 007 gets all the ladies.     - Heh. Batman has Robin.
我们有ESPN台 对吧？
We get ESPN, right?
你何不去穿上你的007燕尾服 我来替你调一杯马丁尼
How about you go put on your 007 tuxedo, and I'll make you a nice martini?
我不喜欢马丁尼
Actually I don't like martinis.
- 那有搞笑吸管的摇摇饮料呢？ - 好的
- A Yoo-Hoo with a funny straw?     - Ooh, yum.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
请帖上写晚上6点
I know the invitation says 6:00...
那是指6点入席 还是6点开始表演？
...but does that mean get there at 6, or the show starts at 6?
"表演"？
The show?
对 婚礼 知道了
Right, the wedding. Gotcha.
不过婚礼会晚一点开始 对不对？
But weddings start a little late, right?
你有参加过我规划的婚礼吗？
Have you ever been to one of my weddings?
那天我外甥女也要受洗…
Ah, well, it's the same day as my niece's christening...
我希望我父母能准时出席来看我
...and I want my parents to see me.
我的部分是在开始时 我不在剩下的表演…婚礼
My part's in the beginning. I'm not in the rest of the show... Wedding.
婚礼6点开始
The wedding starts at 6.
好 我听到了
Okay. I totally hear you.
这样如何？我可以表演到他们到达
Ooh! How about this? I vamp till they get there.
你要"表演"？
Heh. You'll "vamp"?
像是和观众打诨 问他们从哪儿来
Yeah, yeah, like warm up the crowd. Ask where they're from.
因为有乔伊崔比亚尼在 就同时有教士和演艺人员
In Joey Tribbiani, you get a minister and an entertainer.
我是一位"教演人"
I'm a "ministainer."
是吗？
All right?
不会有更好的 不会有更棒的
There's no one better. There's no one greater.
哈？
Huh?
你怎么能不记得我们接吻的事？
How can you not remember us kissing?
不知道 我不记得 很多从没发生过的事
I don't know. I don't remember a lot of things that never happened.
额
Wha...
拜托 记得我们在寝廊里 一直笑一直笑吗？
Remember, we were on the sleeping porch? We couldn't stop giggling.
我们的椰子壳撞在一起
Our coconuts kept knocking together.
乔伊的头在某处爆炸了
Somewhere Joey's head is exploding.
抱歉 我不是想 让你觉得不自在…
I don't want to make you uncomfortable...
但我告诉菲比那件事 她不相信我
...but I told Phoebe it happened, and she doesn't believe me.
对不起 瑞瑞 如果我认为真有那回事 我会承认的
I'm sorry. I mean, if I thought it happened, I would say it.
也许我昏睡过去了 你在我睡觉时对我做了什么
Maybe I passed out and you did stuff to me while I was sleeping.
没有
No.
瑞秋 没关系的 不用这么做 我相信你
It's okay, you don't have to do this. I believe you.
如果你说你吻过梅莉莎 你就是吻过梅莉莎
If you say you kissed Melissa, then you kissed Melissa.
- 谢谢你 菲比   - 好
- Thank you, Phoebe.     - Okay.
- 可是她没有   - 我知道
- But she didn't.     - I know.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你带着它走来走去？
You carry that around?
是的
Yes.
我发现这是个好话题
I find it to be something of a conversation piece.
- 你和…？   - 阿甘
- Between you and?     - Gunther.
我们一起穿上吧
Hey, hey. Why don't we put them on?
拍一张蝙蝠侠和 詹姆士庞德一起的照片
Get a picture of Batman and James Bond, together.
我很乐意 但是我的不合身 裤子小了一点
I would, but my pants are a little tight.
小了一点？我可以看到 里面的两个0和一个7
A little tight? I could see 00 and 7 in those things.
真糟糕 我还很期持 穿着我们的名人燕尾服一起亮相
I was looking forward to wearing our celebrity tuxes together.
- 那表示你不穿你的了？ - 你开玩笑吗？这是蝙蝠侠的燕尾服
- So you're not gonna be wearing yours?     - Are you kidding? It's Batman's tux!
我试穿看看
Let me try it on.
好吧 只有外套 0O和7不要进去
Okay. But just the jacket. 00 and 7 are not getting in there.
好吧
Okay.
双面通风的舒适感 蝙蝠侠
Holy double-vented comfort, Batman!
- 这是什么？ - 哈？
- What's this?     - Huh?
《真情难舍》首映的请柬？
An invitation to the At First Sight premiere?
天啊
Oh, my God.
方基墨没有 在《蝙蝠侠》里穿这件
Val Kilmer didn't wear this in Batman.
他穿这件去参加 他演瞎子的那部文艺爱情片首映
He wore it to the premiere of a fruity love story where he was a blind guy.
给我看
Let me see that.
老天
Oh, man.
你唯一的超能力 是稍微强化的嗅觉
The only super power you have is the slightly heightened sense of smell.
嘿
Hey.
摩妮卡 钱德 可以和你们谈谈吗？
Uh, can I talk to you guys for a second?
算了 我放弃了 你要怎样就怎样吧
I give up. Whatever you want, you can have it.
你要唱歌还是跳舞？
You want to sing a song or do a dance?
还是要你妈在祭坛前 吼出种族歧视的字眼？我都不在乎
You want your mom at the altar screaming racial slurs? I don't care.
我只是要谢谢你们 为我父母做的一切
No. I just want to thank you guys for what you did for my parents.
他们很高兴 能参与你们最特别的一天
They're so happy to get to be a part of your special day.
哦
Oh.
不客气 告诉他们 我们很高兴他们会来
Well, your welcome. Tell them we're glad they're coming.
我会的 给你们看 我婚礼要穿的衣服 他们替我准备的
I will. Oh, check out what they got me to wear for the ceremony!
哈？
Huh?
我替你们证婚时这样戴 然后…
I wear it like this when I marry you guys. And then this...
在宴会时这样戴
...is for party time.
那是真的 我告诉你那发生过
It happened. I am telling you it happened.
很高兴认识你
Hey, it was great meeting you.
还有 瑞秋？我想我不会 打电话给你了 因为…
And, uh, Rachel? I don't think I'll be calling you because, uh...
你变得好奇怪
...you know, you've gotten weird.
保重 两位
Take care, you guys.
等一下 好 听着
Wha... Wait a minute. Okay, look.
那天晚上是我所做过 最狂野的一件事
That night was the one wild thing I've ever done in my life.
我不会让你这样抹煞掉
I won't let you take it away from me.
如果你不记得那件事 也许你会记得这个…
So if you don't remember that, maybe you'll remember this...
我的天 你爱我
Oh, my God. You love me.
- 什么？ - 我当然记得我们的吻
- What?     - Of course I remember our kiss.
我一直想着这件事
I think about it all the time.
我还能听到 椰子壳碰在一起的声音…
I can still hear the coconuts knocking together, I...
我不想告诉你 因为我不觉得 你会回报我的爱 现在你回报…
I didn't want to tell you, because I didn't think you'd return my love.
哇哦…
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
看 你害羞了
Aw! Look who's being suddenly shy.
你一定和我有一样的感觉
You have to feel what I feel.
一定要发自于真心 才能吻得那么好
Nobody can kiss that good and not mean it.
我只是吻功很好
I'm just a good kisser.
闭嘴
Shut up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
啊
Oh.
你不必道歉
Oh, you don't have to be sorry.
我在开玩笑
I'm obviously kidding.
我没爱上你 我没爱上她
I'm not in love with you. I'm not in love with her.
我没听到椰子壳撞在一起的声音
I don't hear coconuts banging together.
我和男友做爱时没幻想你的脸
I don't picture your face when I make love to my boyfriend.
我要走了
Anyway, I gotta go.
吻别一下吧？
A kiss goodbye?
不要？好吧
No? Okay.
喔
Wow!
我完全不知道那会…
I mean, I had no idea that that would...
这是怎么回事？
What the hell was that?
想看看这一场混乱是怎么来的
Just wanted to see what all the fuss was about.
- 然后呢？ - 我有过更好的
- And?     - I've had better.
好 我找到一件合身的
I found one that fits.
是啊 人们常说 第23次就会成功
Well, you know what they say? 23rd time's a charm.
看看你 好英俊
Aw! Look at you, all handsome.
- 谁穿过这件？ - 有关系吗？
- Whose is it?     - Oh, does it matter?
唯一重要的是你看来很英俊
All that matters is that you look so handsome.
- 是谁的？ - 我不想讲
- Whose is it?     - I don't want to say.
我不在乎 是谁的？
Come on, I don't care. Whose is it?
黛安基顿
Diane Keaton.